

ROBERT SANJAYA

CREATIVE FRONT-END DEVELOPER
BASED IN INDONESIA

I am a motivated and trustworthy developer with a Bachelor's Degree in Architecture, building strong front-end skills through self-study. I specialize in Front-end Technologies like Tailwind CSS, Figma, JavaScript Frameworks like React. Passionate about learning and staying updated with the latest industry trends, I combine technical skills, creativity and a business mindset to deliver effective solutions.

EXPERIENCE

2024 - Present Central-Java, Indonesia

2020 – 2022 Central-Java, Indonesia

2016-2019 Villanova, PA (USA)

2007-2016 West Chester, PA (USA)

Creative Developer – Frontend Developer

Actively self-study to master front-end technologies

Business Owner – Autoclean Carwash

Operated a carwash business, overseeing all aspects of the venture from start up to profitability

Assistant Manager – Azie Restaurant

Co-manage all aspects of restaurant operations, including staffing and customer service.

Captain of Waiter - Teikoku Restaurant

Lead a team to taking order, delivering satisfaction service to tables.

SKILLS

- Bilingual: English and Indonesia
- Microsoft Office
- HTML5, CSS3, Tailwind CSS, Figma, React
- Adobe Photoshop

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Architecture Petra Christian University 1999-2003 – Indonesia

CONTACT

I am excited to collaborate on projects with your company and create meaningful impact. I look forward to hear from you.



+62 823-2229-9181



robertolivia777@gmail.com



RobertOlivia777.github.io



/in/robert- sanjaya-14a119289/

EXPERTISE

- Critical thinking
- Creativity
- Management skills
- Leadership